<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Chuck Alt Delete</title>
    <link>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chuck Alt Delete</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 10:46:35 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning DynamoDB</title>
      <link>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/dynamo-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 10:46:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/dynamo-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Foreword From 2021 A while ago, I listened to an amazing podcast episode about DynamoDB decided to do one of AWS’s DynamoDB hands-on tutorials and create a little presentation about what I learned to share at a meetup.
 Enjoy!
    Objectives   Get to know each other
  Compare and contrast DynamoDB data modeling to relational data modeling
  Describe the importance of partitioning in DynamoDB</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to prepare for your DevOps Interview</title>
      <link>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/devops-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 21:42:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/devops-interview/</guid>
      <description>Foreword from 2021 I wrote this post for Insight Data Science in 2019. I&amp;rsquo;ve updated it a tiny bit, but it&amp;rsquo;s mostly the same. It was published on Dzone and the Insight Data Science blog:
 https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-prepare-for-your-devops-interview (40k views!) https://blog.insightdatascience.com/devops-interview-prep-guide-8cd3dc60e587  Introduction Motivation is a great start, but you&amp;rsquo;ll need the discipline to prepare effectively. I&amp;rsquo;ve written this guide to help you develop a disciplined interview preparation routine. Interviewing can really suck - it&amp;rsquo;s random and can make you feel bad about yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World!</title>
      <link>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 18:54:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post for Chuck+Alt+Delete! Welcome!
This site has two purposes:
 &amp;ldquo;learn in public&amp;rdquo; through blog posts host my professional portfolio  Learn in Public I was inspired by the #LearnInPublic hashtag on twitter. Learning in public makes one feel vulnerable, but the upsides in terms of community and learning can be tremendous. Even this post might evolve over time. This is a place for rough draft thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 18:54:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Most of my work these last few years has lived in private repositories, so I&amp;rsquo;ve created this site to do more &amp;ldquo;learning in public.&amp;rdquo; I will keep this page updated with exemplars of my work.
Free Courses As a Senior Curriculum Developer at Confluent, I have written many courses related distributed systems, databases, and stream processing. Most of my courses are only available as a part of a paid subscription, but there are a couple of free samples you can check out.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chuck-alt-delete.github.io/posts/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>portfolio</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
